Would you really do the same thing
in that situation, teach?!
Some pain in life must be
borne with. Remember that.
Stupid freshman like you
don't get to talk back!
Eat shit and die!
Hold on, Kite!
Stay out of it.
He's doing exactly what
Satsuki told us we'd have to.
For real.
Right now, he's bearing all the pain
so that the basketball team can survive.
Kite...
That dumbass!
And it's our responsibility...
...to bear the pain of having
to watch him get beat up like this!
But honestly...
...I don't think this whole "bear the pain" thing
is such a good fit for me.
So without further ado, I'll be introducing
the newest member of the team.
Natsume Kenj-
I'm Kite.
I look forward to playing with you.
I get it.
I'm done. No more fights.
Still, our practice sessions have only been
the same thing over and over.
Don't you have anything else
that we can do, Captain?
Yo, Teach.
Quit staring and try actually
coaching us for once.
You're our advisor, right?
That's true.
Then... how about you do some running?
Dammit, Momoharu. You and your big fat mouth.
Um, Momoharu?
I think we really need someone to help research
and plan a training schedule for us.
You're right. I'll think about it.
Rikukaikuu doko ni ikou
Ahiru no Sora
Kimi o sasoitai na
Monogatari wa hajima tterunda
Okubyou kaze mo recycle
Mayotteru senaka oshite
Give and go! Isogou
Mogutteita honou ga kaodashite
Kakusenai no sa yume ni mita yume
Tobenai tsubasa demo
Bokura wa habataite sora o kanjitai
Naritai jibun ni naritai
Ima dekinai koto mo ashita wa wakannai ze
Waru agaki shiyou
Happy go ducky!
Manager
Yasu! You need to be more
aggressive on defense!
You've left him wide open for a three!
R-right!
Huh?
What was that?
What's wrong? You hurt or something?
No, but I heard a weird
noise from my sneakers...
M-m-my basketball shoes...
have a hole in them!!
Nasuko South
Shopping District
Sports Shop
Suzuki
Hmm... this hole is bad news.
I think it'd be faster if you just bought
an entirely new pair.
Sports Shop
Suzuki
These are an older model, anyway.
Are you sure?
Um...
How about these babies?
They're a new model from AND1.
Buy them now and I'll hook you up with a discount.
Um, no thanks, I'm good.
This totally sucks...
I've been to 5 stores already
and none were willing to fix them for me.
Crap! The next shop is the
very last one on my list!
Sports Nanao
Whatever.
If this place won't do it,
then I'll just have to fix them myself.
Right here. This is it.
NANAO
Excuse me!
Hello?
Whoa. They have a lot more
basketball stuff than I expected.
That might be a good sign!
Coming!
Welcome!
Please wait a moment!
Ow, that hurt!
Huh? Where's the customer?
U-um...
I... can't breathe...
I'm sorry! So Sorry!
I was in such a rush I lost my footing.
Please forgive me!
It's okay. I'm sorry, too.
Um, you're not hurt, are you?
Uh, no!
I'm totally fine thanks to you!
Huh?
You're Kurumatani!
Um... have we met before?
I actually go to the same school as you!
Oh! You're in the class next to mine...
I'm so glad that you remember me!
Uh, yeah.
You stood out to me at the first school assembly,
since we're about the same height.
That's for sure!
My name is Nao Nanao!
Let's be friends!
I'm Sora Kurumatani.
Very cute...
What?
Huh?! Oh, uh, nothing! Never mind!
Um, so, I came here hoping
to get these fixed...
Sure.
Can you wait a sec?
My dad knows way more about
doing repairs than I do.
So I'm gonna go and get him.
Ouch!
U-uh oh, I'm starting to
sense a pattern here...
I'm sorry.
It seems like my dad is
away for the time being.
Would you mind just leaving
your shoes here with us?
Okay.
But even from an amateur
perspective like mine...
I can tell you might be better
off with an entirely new pair.
These days there are a bunch
of different models on the market.
You can easily get a decent
pair for under 10,000 yen.
That's okay.
These are... the only pair I need!
I understand!
I'll take on the responsibility
and make sure they get fixed!
Ouch...!
Um... I think I'd prefer
your dad handled them...
R-right.
Oh, but...
Do you mind,
if I gave you just one piece of advice?
You should at least change the insoles.
Your play style is more focused on speed
than power, Kurumatani.
So, it would be best if you could raise the ankle height
to make it more compatible with your quickness.
They sell a lot of that type
of basketball shoe now,
but if you'd prefer to keep
the ones you have currently,
then there are a few ways
you can customize them for the better.
Wow, that's neat.
I didn't know they had stuff like this.
But wait, how did you know
that my play style focuses on speed?
Well, that's really simple.
Your looks say it all!
Oh... yeah...
Okay then, we'll take
good care of your shoes.
I think it will take about 10 days for us
to make the repairs...
Huh? 10 whole days?!
In the meantime, I'll let you borrow
the pair that I always use.
Wow, a perfect fit. Thanks...
It just kills me that girls' shoes
are always the right size...
Just one more thing... I owe you an apology.
Huh? For what?
I lied to you about something I said earlier.
You lied?
The truth is I was there in the gym,
watching your match with Maru High.
You were so cool, Kurumatani!
Do your best out on the court! Goodnight!
G-goodnight...
Is this for real?!
Does that girl have the hots for me or what?!
No, no, wait a second. Thinking I'm cool
doesn't instantly mean she likes me.
I'm too inexperienced to be
jumping to conclusions, anyway.
But then, why was she getting all blushy?!
I saw the red in her cheeks!
Actually, the real problem is...
...how am I supposed to choose
between her and Madoka?!
Hey, Granny...
What's wrong?
Can you tell me what "love" really is?
Stop acting like such a ninny!
Take a bath and get to bed already!
I can't sleep...
Tomorrow... or I guess it's today now,
we're supposed to have a school assembly.
I'll just go late...
I'm sorry! I was asleep all day!
You're late, Kurumatani.
It's already past the time
for practice to start!
Huh?
Okay, guys! Let's put our
best into practice today!
Yeah!
First, we start with proper warm-ups!
What's gotten into Chiaki and the others?
Well, just take a look.
Huh?
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey, Kurumatani!
WHAAAAT?!
I'm Nao Nanao! From class 1-3!
I'm 144 centimeters tall,
and I weigh 36 kilograms!
I'm a Pisces with a B blood type.
And I love green tea pudding!
Although I may not be the best manager,
I will do my utmost to support the team!
I hope we can get along!
Nanao is... going to be our manager?
She's so tiny!
But super cute.
Th-thank God I chose to
be on the basketball team!
Oh my... she's just like a baby chick.
If you're sharing, I'd love to hear
your body measurements...
Sure! From the top, 71, 5-
Stop! Stop!
Don't ask sleazy questions like those!
And don't answer them!
Why pick us?
Huh?
There's plenty of other
teams looking for a manager.
So why basketball?
M-my reason is...
Be...
Because I like basketball.
She looked at me!
And...
SHE WAS BLUSHING!
Is it a sign? It has to be!
The path to happiness has
finally opened to me!
THIS IS IT!
What's going on with him?
Just ignore it.
He flips out like that a few times a year.
Say, Kurumatani?
This morning...
...why didn't you show up
to the school assembly?
Did you get sick all of a sudden?
U-uh, no, actually... I'm going through
a phase of puberty or something like that...
So I was just asleep the whole day...
Kurumatani.
You skipped every class today,
yet still showed up for practice.
Consequences must not scare you.
Uh, I'm sorry!
I'm assuming that you have a VERY
convincing reason for all of this, Kurumatani.
Huh? Th-the reason...?
Let's hear it, Kurumatani.
Well, you see...
Let's do this!
I'm on fire today!
Yasu!
Shit!
Wow!
Learn to shoot!
A-amazing.
I couldn't tell how he managed
to get that pass through the defense!
What are you doing? It's
time to switch sides!
I'm too sweaty now.
But we just started practice a minute ago!
Rebound!
Wow! That's awesome!
You jump so high! Just like in the NBA!
Of course. That's how we roll.
You're turning into somebody else, Momoharu.
I'm not letting you get away, dammit!
He's fast! And smooth!
He was pulling so many moves in mid-air!
I think he might be kind of cool.
Huh?!
That's not the reaction that we got!
What're you so enraptured by?
Ow, ow, ow...
Are you okay?
Oh, hey, Madoka!
Long time no see.
Yay!
I've missed you so much!
You're just as tiny as ever, Nao.
Never mind me, you've become even more beautiful
since the last time I saw you!
Wish that were me... So lucky.
What's the deal? You old friends?
Oh, yeah.
Since back in middle school.
She was the manager for
the team that I was on.
I owe you so much for all the help
you gave me back then.
Oh, no problem. Same goes for me.
What's up with this weird vibe?
Here!
Stop! Stop!
No more! That's enough!
Your reaction time after receiving
a pass is way too slow.
If you get the ball when you're in shooting range,
the first thing you should do is look at the basket.
Even just a quick glance is okay.
Oh, I get it. We're doing
it to fake them out, right?
Nah. It's to show the defense
that you're serious about trying to score.
Oh! That makes sense.
Sometimes it does lead
to you faking them out.
Just don't forget to do it, okay?
Okay, roger that.
That's great advice, Kite!
I see. You're going to be the
manager for the boys' team.
He's right! No matter what the circumstance,
it's important to always lay on pressure!
So, how are they?
Okay! Let's keep that in mind and try one more time!
Now that you've seen them in action,
what are your thoughts?
W-well... everyone on the team is amazing.
I don't think there are many teams out there
with players of this caliber!
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?!
Please take practice more seriously!
Although...
I don't think this team stands
any chance of winning actual games.
Huh?
Uh, do you think there's
something holding them back?
Well, yes.
Don't be stupid!
What makes you such a prophet
after watching us practice for 5 minutes?
You think you know this game
better than we do, girly?
If that's what she thinks,
then there's no mistake.
Huh?
I can guarantee that personally.
If you'd like, we can even
prove it with a game.
You can play against our girls' team.
What?!
Why?!
A game against the girls' basketball team...?
Hold on, Madoka!
Why on Earth would we ever agree
to put ourselves through that?!
Why not? I don't see the problem with it.
Oh, come on! Just take one
good look at those guys!
You know they'd foul us
just to grab our butts and chests!
It wouldn't take them much to knock us down
and then who knows what would happen!
Hm. That's a rather brilliant strategy.
No, it's really not.
To be honest, I've been wanting
to go up against them for a while now.
I mean, don't you ever get tired
of practicing the same stuff every day?
We should take a break to play sometimes!
But we just played an official
game not too long ago...
Oh yeah.
That reminds me. How did your team do
in the tournament prelims...?
We totally lost. In the very first round.
This is a waste of time.
It's not worth the effort to play against a girls'
team that can't even put up a fight.
I never said that this match
has to be win or lose.
Huh?
It's a good opportunity for you to test your skills
and find out if Nao's assessment is accurate or not.
You don't even have to bother
with winning or losing.
That's all the more reason not to.
None of us are interested
in playing a game that has no stakes.
Especially since we'd be playing
against a bunch of girls.
I just can't bring myself
to take it seriously.
It would just be a waste of time.
You said it.
However!
Well, we could be convinced.
If the girls agree to strip naked when we win,
then I think we could find the motivation!
Gotta put a carrot on the stick, so to speak!
Isn't that even more of a waste of time
than normal practice?
Very well, then.
That's fine.
O..oh-ho?
All the loser has to do is strip down
to the nude, is that right?
W-w-wait a second! What are you saying?!
Then we're all agreed.
Madoka will be the one to do it.
What?
Then we'll play! Without holding back!
Okay!
All right!
Hi-yah!
Wa-tah!
They're already in position to play!
Hold up, Nao. Why's it gotta be me?
Oh well, I thought that you were the one
pushing to have a game against them, Madoka!
Don't worry.
Just leave it all to me!
Owie!
I'm sorry.
I'm just not comfortable leaving
my whole future in your hands.
Ow... ow... ouchies...
Hold on, Momoharu!
You're their captain,
so say something to calm them down!
The hell was that?! What is happening?!
Well, there's no turning back now.
All we can do at this point
is put everything we have into winning.
You guys...!
But in exchange...
...this is all on you if we lose.
Um, okay then.
Starting now, the game between the boys' and girls'
basketball teams will officially begin!
ALL RIGHT!
Doredake sora o miagetatte
Boku wa tobenai to kimi wa itta
Ato nankai te o nobaseba
Todoku no darou to naita yoru
Nigedasu koto ni nareteitte
Sore ga yowasa dato shitta ano hi
Hajimeyou mata, kyou kara
Taisetsu na mono wa itsudemo soba ni atta
Bokura wa itsumo hitori janai donna toki mo
Toberu sa doko made mo kimi wa
Dare yori tataku tataku habataite
Nagashita namida no kazu dake
Tsuyoku narunda
Tsubasa hiroge sekai o megutte
Dare mo shiranai mirai o sagasou
Zutto, zutto, zutto
Aruite yukou saa, issho ni
Ahiru no Sora
Next Time: The Boys' Stubborness
and the Girls' Pride
Next time: "The Boys' Stubbornness
and the Girls' Pride."